[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Cleopatra, Julius Caesar suffered from what ailment?", "correct_answer": "seizures", "incorrect_answers": ["alcoholism", "impotence", "leprosy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "To what continent is the poisonous mushroom known as death cap indigenous?", "correct_answer": "Europe", "incorrect_answers": ["Asia", "Australia", "North America"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The mission statement of NASA is to understand and protect our home planet; to explore the Universe and search for life; and to inspire the next generation of explorers.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which is the most volcanically active body in the Solar System?", "correct_answer": "Jupiters Moon Io", "incorrect_answers": ["Jupiter", "Earth", "Jupiters Moon Europa"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Although you never see him, there is a fisherman who dies on a The Andrea Gails sister boat at the beginning of the movie The Perfect Storm. What was his name?", "correct_answer": "Ben", "incorrect_answers": ["His name is never mentioned", "Bob", "Bill"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The 1973 song Tubular Bells by Mike Oldfield was used for which of the following movies?", "correct_answer": "The Exorcist", "incorrect_answers": ["Rosemarys Baby", "The Shining", "Halloween"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What kind of car is Richard Geres character driving in the movie Pretty Woman?", "correct_answer": "Lotus Esprit", "incorrect_answers": ["Porsche Carrera", "Lamborghini Gallardo", "Lamborghini Murcilago"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these meals would be most suitable for a low carb diet?", "correct_answer": "An apple with cottage cheese", "incorrect_answers": ["Soya sauce", "A ham sandwich", "Meat and potatoes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of meat is used for the preparation of the popular Thai soup called Tom yum?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Prawns", "Fish", "Chicken"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If the world were a village of 1000 people, how many would be from the African continent?", "correct_answer": "149", "incorrect_answers": ["24", "85", "239"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Rescue remedy is a combination of Rock Rose, Star of Bethlehem, Impatiens, Cherry Plum and Clematis essences.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This dessert was made in honor of a famous singer.", "correct_answer": "Peach Melba", "incorrect_answers": ["Cherries Jubalee", "Sacher Torte", "Pineapple upside down cake"]}]